[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is one of the first signs of pregnancy.", "correct_answer": "Missed period", "incorrect_answers": ["Swollen Feet", "Hair loss", "Waddling"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Charles Lindbergh crossed the Atlantic, he had almost no visibility from his front windows.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Quints boat, named after the only natural enemy of the white shark, in Steven Spielbergs horror movie Jaws from 1975?", "correct_answer": "Orca", "incorrect_answers": ["Killer Whale", "Giant Squid", "Moby-Dick"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1951, this city set a new record for the most fans at a basketball game.", "correct_answer": "Berlin", "incorrect_answers": ["New York City", "Melbourne", "Los Angeles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "About how long have ants been around on Earth?", "correct_answer": "60 million years", "incorrect_answers": ["8 million years", "45 milllion years", "25 million years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Freddy Krueger, the villain in \u201cA Nightmare on Elm Street\u201d, was named after which of these?", "correct_answer": "a bully", "incorrect_answers": ["a carpenter who killed his entire family", "the first names of a couple of  burglars", "an old jazz singer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements regarding Slovakia and Slovenia is true?", "correct_answer": "Only Slovenia is an Alpine country.", "incorrect_answers": ["Only Slovakia is an Alpine country.", "None of them is an Alpine country.", "Both are Alpine countries."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 747 was the second airplane designed with a cockpit above the deck.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What excuse did Ferguson use when he was crying on the stand in the movie Sleepers?", "correct_answer": "I was drinking then.", "incorrect_answers": ["I hated the boys.", "Nokes made me do it.", "It was part of the job."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These ancient people drew graffiti on walls and monuments.", "correct_answer": "Romans", "incorrect_answers": ["Hindus", "American Indians", "Moguls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the chemical compound that stands behind vitamin C?", "correct_answer": "L-ascorbic acid", "incorrect_answers": ["L-carnitine", "Citric acid", "Acetylsalicylic acid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who created the Golden Raspberry Awards?", "correct_answer": "John J.W. Wilson", "incorrect_answers": ["Pauline Kael", "Drew Wilson", "Weird Al Yankovic"]}]